# **Bohdan Fedorov**

Backend Developer | Full-stack Developer | DevOps Engineer

Email:bogdanfedorov@gmail.com | Telegram: @Bohdan\_Fedorov\_Web

Ukraine: +380684512382 | Moldova: +37378926053

Github: bogdanfedorov | Linkedin: bohdan-fedorov-137636263 | Djinni:

djinni.co/q/400b4e8e19/

### About me

For the last 3.5 years, I have been working as a web developer, before that I studied to become a software engineer for mobile web applications. Now I work as a DevOps, developing a full stack application, and deploying to servers.

I find ways to solve and implement from a business idea to a deployed solution Constantly learning how to find the best business solutions, sometimes not just about code, but also about business intelligence.

Have experience as a technical lead of a project with 6+ developers, decomposing business requirements into simple tasks for other developers

I already have experience working with AI technologies: OpenAI, T5-model, and Leonardo Ai (a little hate copilot for coding).

## **Education**

### College of Information Systems and Technologies

Kyiv, Ukraine

Lviv Square, 14

Basic computer science and system administration

### The University College of Enterprise and Administration

Lublin, Poland

Bursaki 12

Web and Mobile development, Databases, Java, C#, Python, JS, Business administration

## **Work Experience**

## Freelance (2018-2021)

Lublin, Poland

Trainee - Intern - Junior



### **Yalantis (Sep 2020 - Feb 2022)**

Kyiv, Ukraine

Junior Backend Developer

node.js: express, fastify, nest.js



### Lampa Software (Feb 2022 - Jul 2023)

Vinnica, Ukraine

Junior + Backend Developer | Middle Full-stack

node.js, express, react



# Kvinivel Inc (ex Tesseris Pro) (Oct 2023 - Feb 2024)

\_\_\_\_\_\_

Alberta, Calgary

Middle

node.js,express,react

### Freelance (Feb 2024 - now)

Kyiv, Ukraine

Freelance

## Languages

English (B1)

Ukrainian (Native)

Polish (C1)

Russian (Native)

## Skills & Knowledge

#### BackEnd

- Node.js JS/TS
- GOLANG
- Nest.js, express.js
- GraphQL (Apollo)
- Testing: Jest, Postman scripts, go test
- Documentation: Swagger, JSDoc, TS interfaces
- DB: MongoDB, Postgres, SQLite, Redis
- Orm: TypeOrm, Mongoose

### **DevOps**

- CI/CD
- Docker
- Github, GitLab, BitBucket
- Azure
- Linux
- Python, Bash
- pm2

### FrontEnd

- React.js JS/TS
- Next.js
- HTML, CSS, SEO Schemas
- · Sass, Tailwind

### Other skills

- Code reviewing
- Business Analytics
- Basic system architecture
- Design: Figma
- Test plans and quality assurance
- Internet-marketing
- OpenAI generating SQL and MongoDB aggregation in runtime, generating summary and analytics from a large text source, generating recommendations for rewriting text, assistant for sites like auto FAQ
- T5-model deploying and working. This model generates a revised version of inputted text to contain fewer grammatical errors.

LeonardoAi - image generation

# **Seeking Opportunities**

- Backend Developer specializing in Node.js (express, Nest.js, vanila node.js server) and related technologies.
- Full-stack Developer with expertise in Node.js (express, Nest.js, vanila node.js server) and React.
- DevOps Engineer focusing on CI/CD, Docker, and cloud services.